export const roundedOffQuestionaire = () => {
  return [
    {
      id: 0,
      question: "17 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["10", "20", "17"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "75 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["70", "80", "175"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "64 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["64", "70", "60"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "98 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["80", "100", "89"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "94 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["100", "94", "90"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "445 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["450", "440", "500"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "45 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["50", "45", "40"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "19 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["20", "10", "19"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "0 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["10", "1", "0"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "199 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["190", "100", "200"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "165 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["160", "170", "150"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "999 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
      choices: ["990", "1,000", "909"],
      answer: 1,
    },
  ];
};
